I am cool brother friend thank you to Ajay,
this is this brother-sister, its engine volume is
minimum four stroke single cylinder OHC, I have
protested by noting that off the word
and rain, there are no chances of SMS, isn't it,
then brother its insurance is also
for the next five years, no tension, no worries, China
Bluetooth, brother, you know all this, still you do
n't have a big misconception, the face is a
light part insurance, isn't it, this is third
party insurance, which covers others
but doesn't work for you, the insurance covering damage and fat will
expire after just one year, don't forget to renew it every year,
ah
yes brother sweets, you also don't live in this misconception
and get your two wheeler insurance policy renewed every year from ICICI Lombard
and
avail all the great features like our wide network, boxer garage and inspector